NOTES FOR TRANSLATORS

This file needs to be saved with UTF-16 LE with BOM encoding

Make sure there is a single tab space between the string key ($iEquip_Xxx_Xxx) and the translation, and that there are no additional spaces added at the end of the translation

Where you see \n contained in a string this denotes a new line, and where you see \n\n this denotes a blank line will be left between the two lines

Where you come across nested translations (those where the key names include one or more sets of {} parentheses), each {} represents an additional variable element of text which will be inserted into the translated string at the given points. Explanation of what each element of additional text contains are given on the line above each translation.

$iEquip_swf_EditModeTitleText	iEquip Edit Mode
$iEquip_swf_InstructionsHeaderText	Instructions
$iEquip_swf_NextPrevInstructionText	Select previous/next element
$iEquip_swf_NextPrevToggleText	Press and hold to switch between cycling widget groups and individual elements
$iEquip_swf_MoveInstructionText	Move selected element
$iEquip_swf_ScaleInstructionText	Adjust the size of the selected element
$iEquip_swf_ToggleMoveInstructionText	Press and hold any move/scale button to toggle increments
$iEquip_swf_RotateInstructionText	Rotate the selected element
$iEquip_swf_ToggleRotateInstructionText	Press and hold to toggle rotate increments
$iEquip_swf_RotationDirectionInstructionText	Double tap to change direction of rotation
$iEquip_swf_AlignmentInstructionText	Set text alignment (right/centre/left)
$iEquip_swf_potSelAlignInstTxt	Set potion selector alignment (left/right)
$iEquip_swf_TextColorInstructionText	Press and hold to set text color
$iEquip_swf_AlphaInstructionText	Adjust the opacity of the selected element
$iEquip_swf_ToggleAlphaInstructionText	Press and hold to toggle opacity increments
$iEquip_swf_DepthInstructionText	Bring selected element in front of another
$iEquip_swf_ToggleGridInstructionText	Toggle grid - edge/fullscreen/off
$iEquip_swf_HighlightColorInstructionText	Press and hold to set selected item highlight color
$iEquip_swf_CurrInfoColorInstructionText	Double tap to set selected item info text color
$iEquip_swf_ResetInstructionText	Reset selected element to default
$iEquip_swf_ExitEditModeText	Exit Edit Mode

$iEquip_common_LoadPreset	Load preset
$iEquip_common_SavePreset	Save preset
$iEquip_common_DiscardChanges	Discard changes
$iEquip_common_Unarmed	Unarmed
$iEquip_common_Claws	Claws
$iEquip_common_HealthPotions	Health Potions
$iEquip_common_StaminaPotions	Stamina Potions
$iEquip_common_MagickaPotions	Magicka Potions
$iEquip_common_left	left
$iEquip_common_right	right
$iEquip_common_alteration	Alteration
$iEquip_common_conjuration	Conjuration
$iEquip_common_destruction	Destruction
$iEquip_common_illusion	Illusion
$iEquip_common_restoration	Restoration
$iEquip_common_bound	bound
$iEquip_common_BoundBow	Bound Bow
$iEquip_common_BoundCrossbow	Bound Crossbow
$iEquip_common_BoundArrow	Bound Arrow
$iEquip_common_BoundBolt	Bound Bolt
$iEquip_common_Default	Default
$iEquip_common_Custom	Custom
$iEquip_common_Hidden	Hidden
$iEquip_common_msg_NextPage	Next Page
$iEquip_common_msg_Exit	Exit
$iEquip_common_LoadPresetError	This preset is in an older format and is not compatible with the current version.  The preset has not been loaded to protect against issues which may have arisen as a result.

$iEquip_btn_next	Next Page
$iEquip_btn_exit	Exit
$iEquip_btn_back	Back
$iEquip_btn_controls	Controls
$iEquip_btn_addItems	Adding Items
$iEquip_btn_ammoMode	Ammo Mode
$iEquip_btn_recharge	Recharging
$iEquip_btn_poison	Using Poisons
$iEquip_btn_potGroups	Potion Groups
$iEquip_btn_proMode	Pro Mode
$iEquip_btn_preselect	Preselect Mode
$iEquip_btn_quickRanged	QuickRanged
$iEquip_btn_quickShield	QuickShield
$iEquip_btn_quickHeal	QuickHeal
$iEquip_btn_quickDual	QuickDualCast
$iEquip_btn_queueMenu	Manage Queues
$iEquip_btn_editMode	Enter Edit Mode
$iEquip_btn_helpMenu	Help Menu
$iEquip_btn_refresh	Refresh Widget
$iEquip_btn_debug	Save Queues To File
$iEquip_btn_left	Left Hand
$iEquip_btn_right	Right Hand
$iEquip_btn_shout	Shouts/Powers
$iEquip_btn_cons	Consumables
$iEquip_btn_pois	Poisons
$iEquip_btn_yes	Yes
$iEquip_btn_no	No
$iEquip_btn_confirm	Confirm
$iEquip_btn_cancel	Cancel
$iEquip_btn_carryOn	Carry on editing
$iEquip_btn_discard	Discard changes
$iEquip_btn_delPreset	Delete Preset
$iEquip_btn_clearQueue	Clear Queue
$iEquip_btn_addToQueue	Add to queue

$iEquip_utilitymenu_title	What would you like to do?
$iEquip_queuemenu_title	Which queue would you like to edit?
$iEquip_utilitymenu_notWithWeaponsDrawn	iEquip Utility Menu blocked while weapons drawn
$iEquip_help_title	What would you like help with?
$iEquip_msg_confReset	Are you sure you want to reset this item?
$iEquip_msg_confResetParent	Are you sure you want to reset this widget and all of it's component parts?
$iEquip_msg_confDiscard	Are you sure you want to discard any changes you have made in your current Edit Mode session and reset the widgets to where they were when you entered Edit Mode?
$iEquip_msg_delPreset	Are you sure you want to delete this preset?
$iEquip_msg_clearQueue	Are you sure you want to clear all items from the current queue?

$iEquip_help_addingItems1	Adding items to iEquip\n\nThere are two ways in which you can add items to your queues.  Firstly you can simply carry on equipping items, spells and shouts as normal and each time iEquip detects a new item being equipped it will automagically be added to the relevant queue for you.\n\nAlternatively, you can add items directly from your Inventory, Magic or Favorites menus by simply highlighting any item (you don't need to equip it) and pressing the hotkey for the slot you want to add it to.\n\nPage 1/2

$iEquip_help_addingItems2	When queue items are removed from your inventory (dropped, stored, disarmed, broken, etc) iEquip will remember them and restore them back into the previous queue if they are added back into your inventory.\n\nYou can also use the Queue Management Menus (accessed via the Utility Menu or by holding the Utility Key and double pressing the left/right/shout hotkeys) to remove items, rearrange or clear your queues\n\nEnjoy using iEquip!\n\nPage 2/2

$iEquip_help_AmmoMode1	iEquip Ammo Mode\n\nWhen you equip a ranged weapon the left hand widget will switch to displaying your currently equipped ammo. If you have enabled ammo sorting in the MCM then each time you equip a ranged weapon this will initially be the ammo with the highest base damage, the one you have most of, or the first alphabetically\n\nIn Advanced Ammo Mode, the widget also displays a second smaller icon to the side which shows the item you will re-equip when you unequip your ranged weapon.

$iEquip_help_AmmoMode2	iEquip Advanced Ammo Mode Controls\n\nSingle press left hotkey cycles the ammo\n\nDouble press left hotkey cycles the left hand item shown in the smaller icon ready for re-equipping\n\nCycling your right hand will return the left hand widget to the regular state, or you can longpress the left hotkey to re-equip the left hand item shown and swap your ranged weapon for a 1H item in the right hand

$iEquip_help_recharging1	Recharging enchanted items in iEquip\n\nLong press the left or right hotkeys to recharge the enchanted weapon in that hand. iEquip will select the most appropriate soul to use based on your MCM settings, such as whether you want to use the largest soul that will fit or use up smaller souls first, or if you want to stop iEquip from using souls which are larger than needed to fully recharge the weapon\n\nPage 1/2

$iEquip_help_recharging2	Recharging enchanted items in iEquip\n\niEquip supports GIST - Genuinely Intelligent Soul Trap by opusGlass, so in the MCM you can choose not to use partially filled gems.\n\nYou also have the option of how the current charge is displayed in the widget with either highly customizable charge meters or alternatively dynamic soul gem icons with various levels of fill\n\nPage 2/2

$iEquip_help_poisoning1	Applying Poisons In iEquip\n\nDouble press the left or right hotkeys in regular mode to apply the currently selected poison to the weapon in that hand (left poison application is blocked if a ranged weapon is equipped). In Preselect Mode hold the Utility Key while double pressing.\n\nIf the weapon is already dosed with a different poison you have the option to remove the current one before applying a fresh poison.\nIf the weapon is already dosed with the same poison the charges will stack\n\nPage 1/2

$iEquip_help_poisoning2	Applying Poisons In iEquip\n\nIf the item you are poisoning was equipped by means other than iEquip and is not displayed (auto-add turned off) the poisoning will still work and the poison widget will be updated\n\nThe Charges Per Vial and Multiplier settings below are there to allow you to match poison dosing in iEquip to any other mods you may be using, or to make poisoning a more viable playstyle. Use at your discretion!\n\nPage 2/2

$iEquip_help_potionGroups	Rather than having individual potions in your consumables queue, with Potion Groups turned on you have one queue item each for Health, Stamina and Magicka potions, each displaying a cummulative count of the total number of potions of that type in your inventory. iEquip curates lists of all potions of each type currently in your inventory. Holding the Consumable Key while Potion Group is displayed will consume a potion based on your MCM setting and/or display the Potion Type Selector, allowing you to select and consume a specific type of potion.

$iEquip_help_preselect1	iEquip Preselect Mode\n\nPreselect Mode is toggled by triple pressing your shout hotkey. Up to three new preselect slots will appear, one alongside each main widget slot. Your hotkeys will now cycle the preselect slot allowing you to prepare your next items/shout without actually equipping them.  You then double tap left/right/shout to equip that preelected item, or hold the left or right key to equip all preselected items at once\n\nPage 1/3

$iEquip_help_preselect2	iEquip Preselect Mode\n\nWhen you equip a ranged weapon in Preselect Mode the main left hand slot will switch to displaying your current ammo.\n\nSingle pressing the left hotkey now cycles your ammo.  To cycle the left preselect slot hold the Utility Key and double press left.\nDouble pressing the left hotkey without the Utility Key held equips the left preselected item as before, and switches the right hand to a suitable 1H item.\n\nPage 2/3

$iEquip_help_preselect3	iEquip Preselect Mode\n\nThe preselect icons will only appear for queues with 3 or more items, and you can also choose to disable shout preselect if you'd rather just preselect left/right. In addition to toggling Preselect On/Off manually, you can also choose to toggle out when Equipping All Preselected Items.\n\nWith a bit of forethought Preselect Mode opens up some great new options for tactical gameplay when the going is about to get tough!\n\nPage 3/3

$iEquip_help_quickshield1	iEquip QuickShield\n\nTriple press your left hotkey to scan your left queue for the first available shield or ward spell and equip it automatically. If you choose 'Prefer Magic' then iEquip will look for a ward spell first, and if it doesn't find one will then look for a shield. It will also check if you have a spell equipped in your right hand and if not will search for a destruction spell, or whichever school you have opted to prefer and equip that in your right hand.\n\nPage 1/3

$iEquip_help_quickshield2	iEquip QuickShield\n\nIf you haven't opted to 'Prefer Magic', iEquip will check what you have equipped in your right hand and if it finds anything other than a spell will look for a shield first then a ward, if it finds a spell it will look for a ward first and then a shield. If you currently have a 2H or ranged weapon equipped in your right hand iEquip will search for a suitable 1H item and re-equip the right hand as well.\n\nPage 2/3

$iEquip_help_quickshield3	iEquip QuickShield\n\nYou can also choose to allow QuickShield in Preselect Mode, and specify whether to Preselect or Equip. iEquip will do the same checks on your right hand and 'Prefer Magic' setting, but if you opted to Preselect will only switch the left preselect slot to the found shield or ward. The right preselect slot will not be switched.  Used in combination with Equip All Preselected you can begin to build quite complex three stage attack/equip strategies.\n\nPage 3/3

$iEquip_help_quickRestore1	iEquip QuickRestore and QuickBuff\n\nActivated by triple pressing your consumable key, QuickRestore will intelligently select the most appropriate Restore potion for each enabled stat if required based on your combat state and MCM settings. For Magicka and Stamina this will be with potions, for Health it can also be healing spells.\n\nPage 1/4

$iEquip_help_quickRestore2	iEquip QuickRestore and QuickBuff\n\nIf QuickBuff is enabled, iEquip will immediately, or on a second triple press if specified, select and consume Fortify and/or Regen Rate potions for each stat as well.  With all three types of potions iEquip won't consume if the potion effect is already active on you, meaning potions aren't consumed if not required.\n\nPage 2/4

$iEquip_help_quickRestore3	iEquip QuickRestore and QuickBuff\n\nIn addition to healing potions QuickRestore also gives you the option to prefer magic, in which case iEquip will look for healing spells rather than potions. In either case you have the option to fall back on the alternative healing method if your preferred method isn't found (so potion if it can't find a spell and vice versa. Current health isn't checked before equipping a spell allowing you to equip in advance\n\nPage 3/4

$iEquip_help_quickRestore4	iEquip QuickRestore and QuickBuff\n\nYou can also choose which hand(s) to always equip the spell in, and to enable switching back to your previous items. With this enabled, as long as you haven't cycled either hand in the meantime, a second triple press on your consumable key will switch you back to what you had equipped in both hands before QuickRestore.  You can also choose to find and consume a Restore Magicka potion on switching back to boost your Magicka back up after healing

$iEquip_help_quickranged	iEquip QuickRanged\n\nIf you triple press your right hotkey with QuickRanged enabled iEquip will scan your right queue for the first available ranged weapon of the type selected and equip it automatically. If it doesn't find your first choice of weapon it will then look for one of the alternative type. Very handy for those situations where you need to grab a bow quickly and fire off an opening shot!

$iEquip_help_quickdualcast	iEquip QuickDualCast\n\nIf enabled whenever you cycle to and equip a spell from any of the selected schools iEquip will equip the same spell in both hands allowing you to switch to dual casting with a single action. You can also choose to only allow QuickDualCast if the spell is present in both hand queues. QuickDualCast is disabled in Preselect Mode

$iEquip_help_controls1	Left/Right Hotkeys - Regular Mode\n\nSingle Press - Cycle forward\nUtility Key held + Single Press - Cycle backward\nDouble Press - Apply current poison\nHold - Recharge enchanted item\nTriple Press - QuickShield(L), QuickRanged(R)\nDouble Press (Advanced Ammo Mode) - Cycle left item to be re-equipped\nDouble Press (Torch Equipped) - Drop Lit Torch\n\nPage 1/4

$iEquip_help_controls2	Left/Right Hotkeys - Preselect Mode\nSingle Press - Cycle preselect\nUtility Key held + Single Press - Cycle preselect backwards\nDouble press - Equip preselected item\nHold - Equip all preselected items\nUtility Key held + Double Press - Apply poison\nUtility Key held + Hold L/R - Recharge weapon\nTriple Press - QuickShield(L), QuickRanged(R)\n\nWith Ammo Shown\nSingle Press - Cycle ammo forward\nUtility Key held + Single Press - Cycle ammo backward\nUtility Key held + Double Press - Cycle preselect\n\nPage 2/4

$iEquip_help_controls3	Shout Hotkey\n\nRegular Mode\nSingle Press - Cycle forward\nUtility Key held + Single Press - Cycle backward\n\nPreselect Mode\nSingle Press - Cycle preselect forward\nSingle Press with Utility Key held - Cycle preselect backward\nDouble press - Equip preselected shout/power\n\nAll Modes\nTriple Press - Toggle Preselect Mode On/Off\n\nPage 3/4

$iEquip_help_controls4	Consumable/Poison Hotkey\nSingle Press - Cycle consumable forward\nDouble Press - Cycle poison forward\nUtility Key held + Single Press - Cycle consumable backward\nUtility Key held + Double Press - Cycle poison backward\nHold - Consume current potion/food/drink\nTriple Press - QuickRestore/QuickBuf\n\nUtility Hotkey\nSingle Press - Open Utility Menu\nUtility Key held + Double Press Left/Right/Shout - Quick Access to Queue Menu for that queue (Regular Mode Only)\n\nPage 4/4

$iEquip_WC_lbl_CompleteWidget	Complete widget
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftWidget	Left Hand Widget
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightWidget	Right Hand Widget
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutWidget	Shout Widget
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ConsWidget	Consumable Widget
$iEquip_WC_lbl_PoisonWidget	Poison Widget
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftBg	Left Hand Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftIcon	Left Hand Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftName	Left Hand Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftCount	Left Hand Item Count
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftPoisIcon	Left Hand Poison Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftPoisName	Left Hand Poison Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftAttIcon	Left Hand Attribute Icons
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftMeter	Left Hand Enchantment Meter
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftGem	Left Hand Soul Gem Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftPosInd	Left Queue Position Indicator
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftPreBg	Left Hand Preselect Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftPreIcon	Left Hand Preselect Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftPreName	Left Hand Preselect Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_LeftPreAtt	Left Hand Preselect Attribute Icons
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightBg	Right Hand Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightIcon	Right Hand Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightName	Right Hand Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightCount	Right Hand Item Count
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightPoisIcon	Right Hand Poison Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightPoisName	Right Hand Poison Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightAttIcon	Right Hand Attribute Icons
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightMeter	Right Hand Enchantment Meter
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightGem	Right Hand Soul Gem Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightPosInd	Right Queue Position Indicator
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightPreBg	Right Hand Preselect Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightPreIcon	Right Hand Preselect Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightPreName	Right Hand Preselect Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_RightPreAtt	Right Hand Preselect Attribute Icons
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutBg	Shout Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutIcon	Shout Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutName	Shout Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutPosInd	Shout Queue Position Indicator
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutPreBg	Shout Preselect Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutPreIcon	Shout Preselect Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ShoutPreName	Shout Preselect Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ConsBg	Consumable Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ConsIcon	Consumable Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ConsName	Consumable Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_ConsCount	Consumable Item Count
$iEquip_WC_lbl_potSelector	Potion Type Selector
$iEquip_WC_lbl_PoisonBg	Poison Background
$iEquip_WC_lbl_PoisonIcon	Poison Icon
$iEquip_WC_lbl_PoisonName	Poison Item Name
$iEquip_WC_lbl_PoisonCount	Poison Item Count

$iEquip_WC_common_leftQ	left hand queue
$iEquip_WC_common_rightQ	right hand queue
$iEquip_WC_common_shoutQ	shout queue
$iEquip_WC_common_consQ	consumable queue
$iEquip_WC_common_poisonQ	poison queue

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following three strings will insert the numerical value for the number of potions of that type, for example "Restore (8)"
$iEquip_WC_potionSelector_restore{}	Restore ({})
$iEquip_WC_potionSelector_fortify{}	Fortify ({})
$iEquip_WC_potionSelector_regen{}	Regenerate ({})
$iEquip_WC_not_refreshingWidget	Refreshing iEquip widget...
$iEquip_WC_not_doneRefreshing	iEquip widget refresh complete
$iEquip_WC_msg_addingItems	Adding items to iEquip\n\nBefore you can use iEquip for the first time you need to choose your gear for each slot. Simply open your Inventory, Magic or Favorites menu and follow the instructions there.\n\nAlternatively you can equip items, spells and shouts as normal and each time iEquip detects a new item being equipped it will automatically be added to the relevant queue for you.\n\nEnjoy using iEquip!
$iEquip_WC_msg_inventoryFirstLook	Adding to your iEQUIP queues\n\nFrom within your Inventory, Magic and Favorites menus you can add items, spells, powers or shouts to your iEquip queues by simply highlighting an item (you don't need to equip it) and pressing the hotkey for the slot you want to add it to.
$iEquip_WC_not_controlsUnlocked	iEquip controls unlocked and ready to use

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the name of the widget element which has failed, for example "iEquip: Failed to add element to widget arrays (Left Icon)"
$iEquip_WC_msg_failedToAddWidget{}	iEquip: Failed to add element to widget arrays ({})

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the , for example ""
$iEquip_WC_common_EmptyQueue{}	Your {} is currently empty
$iEquip_WC_not_inOtherhand	is already equipped in your other hand
$iEquip_WC_msg_AmmoModeFirstLook1	iEQUIP Ammo Mode\n\nYou have equipped a ranged weapon for the first time using iEquip and you will see that the left hand widget is now showing the first ammo in your ammo queue. If you have enabled ammo sorting in the MCM then this will either be the ammo with the highest base damage, the one you have most of, or the first alphabetically\nThe smaller icon shows the item you will re-equip when you unequip your ranged weapon.
$iEquip_WC_msg_AmmoModeFirstLook2	iEQUIP Ammo Mode Controls\n\nSingle press left hotkey cycles the ammo\n\nDouble press left hotkey cycles the left hand item shown in the smaller icon ready for re-equipping\n\nCycling your right hand will return the left hand widget to the regular state, or you can longpress the left hotkey to re-equip the left hand item shown and swap your ranged weapon for a 1H item in the right hand

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the name of the hand, for example "You don't currently have a weapon in your right hand to poison"
$iEquip_WC_not_noWeapon{}	You don't currently have a weapon in your {} hand to poison	

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the weapon and poison names, for example "Your Steel Greatsword is already poisoned with Potent Fear Poison"
$iEquip_WC_not_alreadyPoisioned{}{}	Your {} is already poisoned with {}
$iEquip_WC_not_noStaffPoisoning	Hmm... Doesn't seem to work. Strange...

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{}{} in the following string will insert the weapon, hand and poison names, for example "The Iron Sword in your left hand doesn't appear to match what's currently showing in iEquip. Do you wish to carry on and apply Frostbite Venom to it anyway?"
$iEquip_WC_msg_ApplyToUnknownWeapon{}{}{}	The {} in your {} doesn't appear to match what's currently showing in iEquip. Do you wish to carry on and apply {} to it anyway?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{}{} in the following string will insert the weapon, current poison and new poison names, for example "Your Iron Sword is already poisoned with Poison of Damage Health. Would you like to clean it and apply Potent Fear Poison instead?"
$iEquip_WC_msg_CleanApply{}{}{}	Your {} is already poisoned with {}. Would you like to clean it and apply {} instead?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the weapon and poison names, for example "Your Iron Sword is already poisoned with Frostbite Venom. Would you like to add more poison?"
$iEquip_WC_msg_TopUp{}{}	Your {} is already poisoned with {}. Would you like to add more poison?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the poison and weapon names, for example "Would you like to apply Poison of Damage Health to your Steel Greatsword?"
$iEquip_WC_msg_WouldYouLikeToApply{}{}	Would you like to apply {} to your {}?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the weapon name, for example "You currently only have one Iron Sword and it is already in the other hand queue"
$iEquip_WC_msg_InOtherQ{}	You currently only have one {} and it is already in the other hand queue

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the weapon and queue names, for example "You currently only have one Steel Waraxe and it is already in the other hand queue. Do you want to add it to the left hand queue as well?"
$iEquip_WC_msg_AddToBoth{}{}	You currently only have one {} and it is already in the other hand queue. Do you want to add it to the {} as well?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the item and queue name, for example "Would you like to add Scroll of Fireballs to the left hand queue?"
$iEquip_WC_msg_AddToQ{}{}	Would you like to add {} to the {}?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the item and queue names, for example "This Staff of Freezing has already been auto-added to the right hand queue. Would you like to remove..."
$iEquip_WC_msg_RemoveAAFlag{}{}	This {} has already been auto-added to the {}. Would you like to remove the 'auto-added' flag? If you have enabled 'Skip Auto-Added Items' while cycling in the MCM removing the flag from this item will allow it to show as normal when cycling the queue.

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the queue name, for example "The shout queue is full"
$iEquip_WC_not_QIsFull{}	The {} is full

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the item and queue names, for example "Unrelenting Force was added to the shout queue"
$iEquip_WC_not_AddedToQ{}{}	{} was added to the {}

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the item and current queue names, for example "Steel Waraxe has already been added to the right hand queue"
$iEquip_WC_not_AlreadyAdded{}{}	{} has already been added to the {}
$iEquip_WC_not_AAFlagRemoved	Auto-Added flag removed
$iEquip_WC_msg_failToAdd	You are trying to add the wrong type of item or spell to one of your iEquip queues.\n\nRULES\nLeft hand queue - 1H weapons, unarmed, staffs, spells, scrolls, torch, shield\nRight hand queue - Any weapon, spells, scrolls\nShout queue - shouts, powers\nConsumable queue - potions, food, drink\nPoison queue - poisons

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the item and queue names, for example "Unrelenting Force cannot be added to the left hand queue"
$iEquip_WC_not_CannotAdd{}{}	{} cannot be added to the {}

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{}{} in the following string will insert the weapon, weapon and queue names, for example "Are these Throwing Axes classed as throwing weapons? ... Would you like to proceed and add Throwing Axes to the left hand queue?"
$iEquip_WC_msg_throwingWeapons{}{}{}	Are these {}s classed as throwing weapons?\n\nPlease note that the javelins from Spears by Soolie are classed as arrows or bolts and should not be added here.\n\nWould you like to proceed and add {}s to the {}?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the numerical count and queue name, for example "You currently have 7 items in your right hand queue"
$iEquip_WC_lbl_titleWithCount{}{}	You currently have {} items in your {}
$iEquip_WC_msg_deletePotionGroup	You have just removed one of the potion groups from your consumables queue. These can be added back at any time via the Potions page in the MCM.

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the queue name, for example "Your left hand queue has been cleared"
$iEquip_WC_msg_QCleared{}	Your {} has been cleared

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the potion group name, for example "The Health Potions group has been re-enabled. Would you like to..."
$iEquip_WC_msg_RemovePotionsFromConsumableQueue{}	The {} group has been re-enabled. Would you like to remove any individual potions from the consumable queue now?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the potion group name, for example "The Health Potions group has been removed.  Would you like to..."
$iEquip_WC_msg_PotionGroupRemoved{}	The {} group has been removed.  Would you like to add the individual potions to the consumable queue now?

$iEquip_PM_lbl_EMdummyShout	Something Loud and Shouty
$iEquip_PM_lbl_EMdummySword	Pointy Hurty Thing
$iEquip_PM_msg_firstLook	iEQUIP Preselect Mode\n\nYou should now see up to three new slots in the widget for the left, right and shout slots, as long as you have more than two items in each of the queues and haven't disabled the shout slot\nThe hotkeys now cycle the preselect slots. Hold the utility key down and double tap a hotkey to equip the preselected item.\nHold the utility key down and press and hold the left or right keys to equip all preselected items in one go.\nTriple press the shout key to exit Preselect Mode
$iEquip_PM_msg_firstRanged	iEquip Ammo Mode\n\nYou have equipped a ranged weapon in your right hand in Preselect Mode for the first time.  You will see that the main left hand slot is now displaying your current ammo.\n\nControls while ammo shown\n\nSingle press left hotkey cycles ammo\nDouble press left hotkey cycles preselect slot\nLongpress left hotkey equips the left preselected item and switches the right hand to a suitable 1H item.
$iEquip_PM_not_QRNoRanged	iEquip couldn't find a ranged weapon or bound spell to equip
$iEquip_PM_not_HealthFull	No need to QuickRestore health
$iEquip_PM_not_noHealthBuffPotions	You have no health buff potions left
$iEquip_PM_not_StaminaFull	No need to QuickRestore stamina
$iEquip_PM_not_noStaminaBuffPotions	You have no stamina buff potions left
$iEquip_PM_not_MagickaFull	No need to QuickRestore magicka
$iEquip_PM_not_noMagickaBuffPotions	You have no magicka buff potions left
$iEquip_PM_not_PrefMagicHealthFull	You have yet to master a healing spell and are not in need of a healing potion
$iEquip_PM_not_QHNotFound	iEquip couldn't find a healing potion or spell to equip
$iEquip_PM_not_QSNotFound	iEquip QuickShield did not find a shield or ward in your left hand queue
$iEquip_PM_heal	heal

$iEquip_RC_not_petty	Petty soul consumed
$iEquip_RC_not_lesser	Lesser soul consumed
$iEquip_RC_not_common	Common soul consumed
$iEquip_RC_not_greater	Greater soul consumed
$iEquip_RC_not_grand	Grand soul consumed
$iEquip_RC_not_alreadyFull	This weapon is already fully charged
$iEquip_RC_not_noSoul	No soul found

$iEquip_AM_not_noAmmo	You do not appear to have any ammo to equip for this type of weapon

$iEquip_EM_msg_firstBringToFront	This feature allows you to adjust the layer order of the elements within each widget, and the layer order of the widgets themselves\n\nYou cannot bring an element of one widget in front of one from another widget, only elements within the same widget\n\nIt is disabled for backgrounds and when the complete widget is selected for obvious reasons

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the widget element name, for example "Now select the item you want to move the Right Name in front of..."
$iEquip_EM_msg_bringToFrontSelNext{}	Now select the item you want to move the {} in front of and press the Bring To Front key a second time
$iEquip_EM_not_bringToFrontError	Error: The selected elements are not part of the same widget
$iEquip_EM_not_settingDepth	Setting depth
$iEquip_EM_clockwise	Clockwise
$iEquip_EM_counterClockwise	Counterclockwise
$iEquip_EM_degrees	degrees
$iEquip_EM_pixels	pixels
$iEquip_EM_leftAligned	Left aligned
$iEquip_EM_rightAligned	Right aligned
$iEquip_EM_centreAligned	Centre aligned
$iEquip_EM_potSelLeft	For left of potion icon
$iEquip_EM_potSelRight	For right of potion icon
$iEquip_EM_edgeGrid	Edge grid
$iEquip_EM_fullGrid	Fullscreen grid
$iEquip_EM_msg_cycleHelp	!!! IMPORTANT INFORMATION !!!\n\nCycling elements in Edit Mode\n\nSINGLE PRESS the keys shown at the top of the instructions panel to cycle through the widget elements.\n\nPRESS AND HOLD either key to switch from cycling the widget groups to cycling the individual elements.
$iEquip_EM_somePoison	Some horrible poison
$iEquip_EM_somePower	Some Awesome Power
$iEquip_EM_somePotion	Some Useful Potion
$iEquip_EM_lbl_presetListTitle	Select a widget preset to load
$iEquip_EM_not_layoutSwitched	Widget layout switched to
$iEquip_EM_not_noPresets	No saved presets found
$iEquip_EM_lbl_showColorTitle1	Select a color for selected item highlights
$iEquip_EM_lbl_showColorTitle2	Select a color for selected item info text
$iEquip_EM_lbl_showColorTitle3	Select a text color for selected text element
$iEquip_EM_lbl_enterHex	Enter a custom colour hex code
$iEquip_EM_lbl_namePreset	Name this layout preset
$iEquip_EM_not_savedAs	Current layout saved as
$iEquip_EM_not_resetting	Resetting iEquip...
$iEquip_EM_not_doneResetting	Finished resetting iEquip

$iEquip_PO_restoreHealth	restore health
$iEquip_PO_fortifyHealth	fortify health
$iEquip_PO_regenHealth	health regeneration rate
$iEquip_PO_restoreMagicka	restore magicka
$iEquip_PO_fortifyMagicka	fortify magicka
$iEquip_PO_regenMagicka	magicka regeneration rate
$iEquip_PO_restoreStamina	restore stamina
$iEquip_PO_fortifyStamina	fortify stamina
$iEquip_PO_regenStamina	stamina regeneration rate
$iEquip_PO_PotionConsumed	consumed

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the stat name, for example "You do not appear to have any suitable stamina potions left"
$iEquip_PO_not_noneLeft{}	You do not appear to have any suitable {} potions left

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the stat name, for example "You are currently at full health"
$iEquip_PO_not_AVFull{}	You are currently at full {}

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the potion type, for example "The effects of your previous Fortify Health potion have not yet worn off"
$iEquip_PO_not_EffectActive{}	The effects of your previous {} potion have not yet worn off

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the potion type, for example "That was the last of your Restore Health Potions"
$iEquip_PO_not_allOutOfRestorePotions{}	That was the last of your Restore {}

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the potion type, for example "You're down to your last few Restore Health Potions"
$iEquip_PO_not_nearlyOutOfRestorePotions{}	You're down to your last few Restore {}

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the potion type, for example "You're getting pretty low on Restore Health Potions"
$iEquip_PO_not_notManyRestorePotionsLeft{}	You're getting pretty low on Restore {}

$iEquip_TO_not_noTorch	You do not have a torch to equip

$iEquip_MCM_common_lbl_WidgetOptions	Widget Options
$iEquip_MCM_common_seconds	seconds
$iEquip_MCM_common_minutes	minutes
$iEquip_MCM_common_reset	Reset
$iEquip_MCM_common_cancel	Cancel
$iEquip_MCM_common_opt_disabled	Disabled
$iEquip_MCM_common_notDetected	Not detected
$iEquip_MCM_common_installed	Installed

$iEquip_MCM_not_Updating	Updating iEquip to Version
$iEquip_MCM_not_ApplyingSettings	Applying iEquip settings...
$iEquip_MCM_not_Disabled	iEquip disabled...
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_General	General Settings
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Hotkey	Hotkey Options
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Queue	Queue Options
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Potions	Potions
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Recharging	Recharging and Poisoning
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Torch	Immersive Torches
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Pro	Advanced
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Misc	Misc UI Options
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Edit	Edit Mode
$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Info	Information

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {}{} in the following string will insert the mod name and control, for example "This key is already mapped to: Wearable Lanterns\Toggle Lantern Are you sure you want to continue?"
$iEquip_MCM_msg_AlreadyMapped1{}{}	This key is already mapped to:\n\"{}\"\n{}\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?

NOTE FOR TRANSLATORS - The {} in the following string will insert the mod name, for example "This key is already mapped to: Wearable Lanterns Are you sure you want to continue?"
$iEquip_MCM_msg_AlreadyMapped2{}	This key is already mapped to:\n\"{}\"\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?

$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_Unsorted	Unsorted
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_ByDamage	By damage
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_Alphabetically	Alphabetically
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_ByQuantity	By quantity
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_DoNothing	Do nothing
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_SwitchNothing	Switch/Do nothing
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_SwitchCycle	Switch/Cycle
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_Cycle	Cycle right hand
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_onlyCycling	While cycling
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_alwaysVisible	Always visible
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_onOff	iEquip On/Off
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_showTooltips	Show Tooltips
$iEquip_MCM_gen_msg_showTooltips	If this is the first time you have used iEquip, or you are not yet familiar with all of the features and controls, we strongly recommend you leave tooltips enabled.\n\nAre you sure you want to disable tooltips?
$iEquip_MCM_gen_mes_transformBackFirst	Before enabling iEquip please transform back into your regular form.\n\nThe next time you transform into werewolf, vampire lord or lich form iEquip will adapt itself to the new form by hiding any parts of the widget and disabling hotkeys not relevant for equipping in the new form.
$iEquip_MCM_gen_msg_skipBlocksPosInd	Queue Position Indicators are disabled as you currently have 'Skip auto-added items when cycling' enabled in the Queue Options page 
$iEquip_MCM_common_lbl_firstEnabled1	Please exit back out of the journal menu
$iEquip_MCM_common_lbl_firstEnabled2	and wait for the widget to show before
$iEquip_MCM_common_lbl_firstEnabled3	changing any iEquip settings in the MCM
$iEquip_MCM_common_lbl_firstEnabled4	Some unequipping and re-equipping may
$iEquip_MCM_common_lbl_firstEnabled5	occur whilst iEquip is initialising.
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_enblShoutSlt	Enable shout slot
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_enblConsumSlt	Enable consumables slot
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_enblPoisonSlt	Enable poisons slot
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_AmmoMode	Ammo Mode Options
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_AmmoModeChoice	Ammo Mode Style
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_ammoLstSrt	Ammo list sorting
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_whenNoAmmoLeft	When no ammo left
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_simpleAM	Simple
$iEquip_MCM_gen_opt_advAM	Advanced
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_Cycling	Cycling behaviour
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_eqpPaus	Equip on pause
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_eqpPausDelay	Equip on pause delay
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_queuePosInd	Queue position indicators
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_showAtrIco	Show attribute icons
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_AddUnarmed	Add 'Unarmed' shortcut to right queue
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_VisGear	Visible Gear Options
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_enblAllGeard	Enable All Geared Up
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_autoUnqpAmmo	Auto Unequip Ammo
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_BeastMode	Player Transformations
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_BM_werewolf	Enabled in werewolf form
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_BM_vampLord	Enabled in Vampire Lord form
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_BM_lich	Enabled in Lich form
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_onOff	When enabling iEquip here, please exit out of the Journal Menu, then re-open the iEquip MCM to complete the installation.
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_showTooltips	Help messages are displayed at various points, giving instructions on how to use certain features.  If you are familiar with iEquip, you can turn these off here.  All of the information contained in the tooltips is also available in game at any time through the Help Menu option in the Utility Menu.
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_enblShoutSlt	Enable the shout slot in the widget\nDefault: Enabled
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_enblConsumSlt	Enable the consumable slot in the widget. Also disables the consume item feature.\nYou can still choose to have the poison slot enabled, even if the consumable slot is disabled.\nDefault: Enabled
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_enblPoisonSlt	Enable the poison slot in the widget. Also disables all poisoning features.\nIf you have disabled the consumable slot, then you can cycle your poisons with a single press rather than a double press.\nDefault: Enabled
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_ammoLstSrt	iEquip curates lists of arrows and bolts currently in your inventory and updates them whenever ammo is added or removed. You can optionally choose to have the resultant list sorted by damage, alphabeticall, or by current quantity. If sorting 'By damage' the strongest available ammo will be equipped first, while sorting 'By quantity' will result in equipping the most plentiful ammo of the given type in your inventory at the time\nDefault = By damage
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_whenNoAmmoLeft	Choose what happens when you run out of ammo for your equipped ranged weapon\nDo Nothing - Left slot will remain empty until you obtain more ammo\nSwitch/Do Nothing - Equip an alternative ranged weapon, if you have the correct ammo for it, otherwise do nothing.\nSwitch/Cycle - As above, but if no suitable alternative found, cycle as detailed below.\nCycle - Cycle your right hand, or if using QuickRanged, switch out according to the QuickRanged settings.\nDefault = Switch / Cycle
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_AmmoModeChoice	Advanced - Ammo shows in the left slot with left hand preselect to the side, showing the item to be equipped in your left hand when you cycle to a non-ranged weapon in your right. Allows cycling of both ammo (left single press) and preselect (left double tap). Press and hold left to equip the preselect item and find and equip a 1H item in the right hand.\nSimple - Ammo displays and can be cycled in the left slot, with no preselect.\nDefault: Advanced
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_eqpPaus	With Equip On Pause enabled, you can cycle through as many items as you like until you find what you want. Only once you stop cycling will the selected item equip, after the delay set below.\nIf you disable Equip On Pause, each time you cycle a slot the item will be equipped immediately. This option is best suited for a small number of items, as cycling through many items, equipping each in turn, may be slower.\nDefault: ON
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_showPosInd	Enable queue position indicators which show the position of the currently equipped item, and the current position while cycling. Choose whether to only show the position indicators while cycling, or to have them permanently displayed
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_showAtrIco	Show small icons indicating item is poisoned and/or enchanted next to the item icons in the main left and right slots whilst cycling, and in the left and right preselect slots when Preselect Mode is active.
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_addFists	Add the 'Unarmed' shortcut back into your right hand queue. Cycling to this will unequip both hands, for whenever you just feel like a good old-fashioned punch-up!
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_enblAllGeard	Enables the vanilla Geared Up feature which is disabled by default. This allows you to display favorited items on your character when not equipped. iEquip uses the same methods as Equipping Overhaul and Visible Favorited Items as workrounds to the bugs with the vanilla implementation.\nDefault: Off
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_autoUnqpAmmo	When enabled, any currently equipped ammo will be unequipped when you no longer have a ranged weapon equipped, removing the quiver from your character when not wielding a bow or crossbow.\nDefault: On
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_BM_werewolf	If enabled the widget will be displayed whilst you are in werewolf form.  The consumable and poison slots will be hidden and all Pro Mode functions are disabled.  No equipping actions are available in werewolf form as you only have claws and your howl, so all iEquip controls are disabled and the widget is displayed for information only
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_BM_vampLord	If enabled the widget will be displayed whilst you are in Vampire Lord form.  The consumable and poison slots will be hidden and all Pro Mode functions are disabled.  As you equip spells and powers normally through the vanilla menu they will be added to your Vampire Lord queues and become available through iEquip.  The widget will also switch to displaying claws when you stop levitating.
$iEquip_MCM_gen_txt_BM_lich	If enabled the widget will be displayed whilst you are in Lich form.  The consumable and poison slots will be hidden and all Pro Mode functions are disabled.  As you equip spells normally through the Undeath spell menu they will be added to your Lich queues and become available through iEquip.

$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_htkHelp	Show hotkey help
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_MainHtks	Main Hotkeys
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_leftHand	Left Hand Hotkey
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_rightHand	Right Hand Hotkey
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_shout	Shout Hotkey
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_consumPoison	Consumable/Poison Hotkey
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_UtHtkOpts	Utility Hotkey Options
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_util	Utility Hotkey
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_KeyPressOpts	Key Press Options
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_multiTapDelay	Multi-Tap Delay
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_longPrsDelay	Long Press Delay
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_ExtKbCtrls	Extended Keyboard Controls
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_enblExtKbCtrls	Enable extended keyboard controls
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_consItem	Consume Item
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_cyclePoison	Cycle Poisons
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_quickRestore	QuickRestore
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_quickShield	QuickShield
$iEquip_MCM_htk_lbl_quickRanged	QuickRanged
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_htkHelp	Show a full description of what actions are available on each hotkey
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_leftHand	Select a hotkey to control the left hand widget functions\nDefault: G
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_rightHand	Select a hotkey to control the right hand widget functions\nDefault: H
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_shout	Select a hotkey to control the shout widget functions\nDefault: Y
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_consumPoison	Select a hotkey to control the consumable and poison widgets functions\nDefault: B
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_util	Select a hotkey for accessing various menus and modes\nDefault: K
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_multiTapDelay	This defines the maximum delay there can be between key presses for them to register as a multi-tap (double/triple press)\nSet this to the minimum time in which you can comfortably execute a multi-tap\nDefault: 0.3 seconds
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_longPrsDelay	This defines the length of time you need to hold a key down for for it to register as a Long Press\nThis does not conflict with the multi-tap setting so set it to whatever you are comfortable with, but not so short that every key press is classed as a Long Press!\nDefault: 0.6 seconds
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_enblExtKbCtrls	This allows you to set up to six additional hotkeys giving direct single press access to a range of iEquip functions. If you are using a controller we recommend you set these as keyboard shortcuts here, then use Gamepad++ to set some of your additional key combos to emulate them.\nDefault: Off
$iEquip_MCM_htk_txt_optHotKey	Set a hotkey to provide direct single press access to this function

$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_EMOptions	Edit Mode Options
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_slowTimeStr	Slow Time effect strength
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_EMKeys	Edit Mode Keys
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_chooseHtKey	Choose your hotkeys
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_nextElem	Next element
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_prevElem	Previous element
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_moveUp	Move up
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_moveDown	Move down
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_moveLeft	Move left
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_moveRight	Move right
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_sclUp	Scale up
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_sclDown	Scale down
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_rotate	Rotate
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_adjTransp	Adjust opacity
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_bringFrnt	Bring to front
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_setTxtAlCo	Set text alignment and colour
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_tglRulers	Toggle rulers
$iEquip_MCM_edt_lbl_rstSelElem	Reset selected element
$iEquip_MCM_edt_txt_slowTimeStr	iEquip Edit Mode runs with the game unpaused, so to avoid unneccessary death or injury while you set things up we apply a slow time effect. This slider lets you set how much time slows by in Edit Mode\nDefault is 100% or fully paused, at 0 time passes normally in Edit Mode
$iEquip_MCM_edt_txt_chooseHtKey	Choose to use the recommended Edit Mode hotkeys or set your own

$iEquip_MCM_ui_degrees	degrees
$iEquip_MCM_ui_pixels	px
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_Single	Single
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_Triple	Triple
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_Quiver	Quiver
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_NoBg	No background
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_SqBBg	Square with border
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_SqNoBBg	Square without border
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_RoBBg	Round with border
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_RoNoBBg	Round without border
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_RoFade	Round with fade
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_Dialogue	Dialogue style
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_Slow	Slow
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_Normal	Normal
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_Fast	Fast
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_CycleSlot	Cycle slot
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_ShowName	Show name
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt0	Don't show
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt1	Iron Sword (Fine)
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt2	Iron Sword (Fine, 60%)
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt3	Iron Sword - Fine
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt4	Iron Sword - Fine (60%)
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt5	Iron Sword - Fine, 60%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt6	Iron Sword, Fine
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt7	Iron Sword, Fine (60%)
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt8	Iron Sword, Fine - 60%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt9	Fine Iron Sword
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt10	Fine Iron Sword (60%)
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt11	Fine Iron Sword, 60%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvlTxt12	Fine Iron Sword - 60%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_noColor	Don't colour
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_colorLower	Unfaded section only
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_colorFull	Full icon
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvl4020	40% / 20%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvl3020	30% / 20%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvl3010	30% / 10%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_opt_tmpLvl2010	20% / 10%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_posIndOpts	Queue Position Indicator Options
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_posIndColor	Position indicator colour
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_posIndAlpha	Position indicator opacity
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_currPosIndColor	Current position indicator colour
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_currPosIndAlpha	Current position indicator opacity
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_temperedItemOpts	Tempered Item Options
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_tmpLvlTxt	Name style
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_tempInfoBelow	Temper level below item name
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_tempLvlFade	Fade icon as item degrades
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_tempLvlColorIcon	Coloured icons
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_tempLvlThresholds	Change colour at
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_iconBgOpts	Misc Icon & Background Options
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_fadeLeftIco2h	Fade left icon if 2H equipped
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_leftIcoFade	Left icon fade
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_ammoIcoStyle	Ammo icon style
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_bckgroundStyle	Background style
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_txtShadOpts	Text Drop Shadow Options
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_dropShadow	Show drop shadow on text
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_dropShadowAlpha	- Opacity
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_dropShadowAngle	- Angle
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_dropShadowBlur	- Blur
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_dropShadowDistance	- Distance
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_dropShadowStrength	- Strength
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_fadeoutopts	Fade Out Options
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_enblWdgetFade	Enable widget fadeout
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_wdgetFadeDelay	Widget fadeout delay
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_wdgetFadeSpeed	Widget fadeout animation speed
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_wdgetFadeDur	Widget fadeout duration
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_visWhenWeapDrawn	Always visible when weapons drawn
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_enblNameFade	Enable name fadeouts
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_leftRightNameFade	Fadeout left & right item names
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_shoutNameFade	Fadeout shout/power name
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_consPoisNameFade	Fadeout consumable & poison names
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_mainNameFadeDelay	Main name fadeout delay
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_poisonNameFadeDelay	Poison name fadeout delay
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_preselectNameFadeDelay	Preselect name fadeout delay
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_nameFadeSpeed	Name fadeout animation speed
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_nameFadeDur	Name fadeout duration
$iEquip_MCM_ui_lbl_firstPressNameHidn	First press when name hidden
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_posIndColor	Select the colour for the current cycling position bar in the queue position indicators
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_posIndAlpha	Set the level of opacity for the current cycling position bar in the queue position indicators.  The general opacity of the complete indicators can be set as normal in Edit Mode, this only affects the current position bar in addition to that.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_currPosIndColor	Select the colour for the currently equipped item position bar in the queue position indicators
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_currPosIndAlpha	Set the level of opacity for the currently equipped item position bar in the queue position indicators.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_tmpLvlTxt	Choose if and how you would like the temper level name and numerical percentage value to be displayed in the item names
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_tempInfoBelow	Show the temper level name and/or numerical value on a separate line below the item name
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_tempLvlFade	If you are using an item tempering and degradation mod such as Loot & Degradation, then with this setting enabled, as your weapons or shields degrade the icon will begin to fade out from top to bottom, representing the current temper level percentage.  The degraded section is not completely faded out, so you can still see the complete icon.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_tempLvlColorIcon	Allows you to choose whether or not to colour the icons as items become badly degraded within the current temper level.  Additionally you can choose whether to colour just the unfaded lower section of the icon, leaving the faded section white, or to colour the full icon including the faded section.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_tempLvlThresholds	Choose at what points within the current temper level you would like the icon to turn amber and then red.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_fadeLeftIco2h	If enabled the left hand icon will be faded when a 2H or ranged weapon is equipped in the right hand\nDefault: Enabled
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_leftIcoFade	Choose how much you would like the left icon faded out by.\nDefault: 70%
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_ammoIcoStyle	Choose the style of arrow/bolt icons which will display in the left hand slot when you have a ranged weapon equipped. All styles will also display an enchantment type icon if special arrows are equipped (fire, ice,shock, etc)\nSingle - A single default arrow or bolt icon\nTriple - three default arrow or bolt icons of varied size\nQuiver - Arrow or bolt quiver icons\nDefault: Single
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_bckgroundStyle	Choose the style for your slot backgrounds.\nBackgrounds can be scaled, rotated and faded in Edit Mode\nDefault: No Background
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_dropShadow	This allows you to disable the drop shadow effect on the text elements in the widget\nDefault: Enabled
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_dropShadowAlpha	Adjust the opacity (alpha) of the drop shadow effect on the text elements in the widget
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_dropShadowAngle	Adjust the offset angle of the drop shadow effect on the text elements in the widget
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_dropShadowBlur	Adjust the blur (spread) of the drop shadow effect on the text elements in the widget
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_dropShadowDistance	Adjust the offset distance of the drop shadow effect on the text elements in the widget
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_dropShadowStrength	Adjust the strength (contrast) of the drop shadow effect on the text elements in the widget
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_enblWdgetFade	Enables widget fadeout after a period of inactivity.  Once enabled additional fadeout options will become available to you\nDefault is Disabled
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_wdgetFadeDelay	The time in seconds of inactivity after which the iEquip widget will fade out\nSetting this to zero will disable the fadeout\nDefault delay = 30 seconds
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_wdgetFadeDur	The duration in seconds of the widget fade out animation\nSetting this to zero will make the widget hide instantly after the delays set above\nDefault duration = 1.5 seconds
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_visWhenWeapDrawn	Ensures that the widget will always be visible when you have your weapons drawn.  If the widget is currently faded out when you draw your weapons it will automatically be re-shown\nDefault is Enabled
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_enblNameFade	Enables fadeout of item names after cycling.  Once enabled additional fadeout options will become available to you\nDefault is Disabled
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_leftRightNameFade	Left and right item names, poison names and preselected item names will fade out after cycling or equipping.  The fadeout delays for name, poison and preselect name are independent and can be adjusted below.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_shoutNameFade	Shout/power names will fade out after cycling or equipping.  The fadeout delay can be adjusted below.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_consPoisNameFade	Consumable and poison names will fade out after cycling.  The main name fadeout delay, shared with the left/right item names, controls when they fade out can be adjusted below.
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_mainNameFadeDelay	The time in seconds after cycling the main slots after which the main item names text will fade out\nSetting this to zero will disable the fadeout\nDefault delay = 5.0 seconds
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_poisonNameFadeDelay	The time in seconds after cycling the main slots after which the poison names text will fade out\nSetting this to zero will disable the fadeout\nDefault delay = 5.0 seconds
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_preselectNameFadeDelay	The time in seconds after cycling the preselect slots after which the preselect item names text will fade out\nSetting this to zero will disable the fadeout\nDefault delay = 5.0 seconds
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_nameFadeSpeed	The speed of the fadeout animation for the item name text\nDefault: Normal (1.5 seconds)
$iEquip_MCM_ui_txt_nameFadeDur	The duration in seconds of the names fade out animation\nSetting this to zero will make the text hide instantly after the delays set above\nDefault duration = 1.5 seconds

$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_Hidden	Hidden
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_Meters	Charge Meters
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_Soulgem	Dynamic Soulgem
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_left	left
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_right	right
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_both	both
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_ShowAll	Show All
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_TopUpSw	Top-up & Switch
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_DntShow	Don't show
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_Count	Count Only
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_DropCount	Single Drop & Count
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_Drop	Single Drop
$iEquip_MCM_rep_opt_Drops	Multiple Drops
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_showEnchRechHelp	Show Enchantment Recharging Help
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_enblEnchRech	Enable enchanted weapon recharging
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_soulgemUseOpts	Soulgem Use Options
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_useLargSoul	Use largest available soul
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_useOvrsizSoul	Use oversized souls
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_usePartGem	Use partially filled gems
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_showEnchCharge	Charge displayed as
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_enableChargeFadeout	Enable enchantment charge fadeout
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_chargeFadeDelay	Fadeout delay
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_fadeAfter	Fade after
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_normFillCol	Normal charge fill colour
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_enableCustomFlashCol	Enable custom flash colour
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_meterFlashCol	Empty warning flash colour
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_changeColLowCharge	Change colour on low charge
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_setLowChargeTresh	Set low charge threshold
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_lowFillCol	Low charge fill colour
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_enableGradientFill	Enable gradient fill
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_gradFillCol	Gradient (low) fill colour
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_leftFillDir	Left meter fill direction
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_rightFillDir	Right meter fill direction
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_PoisonsDisabled1	Poisoning features are currently disabled.
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_PoisonsDisabled2	If you wish to use the poisoning features
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_PoisonsDisabled3	please re-enable the Poison Widget in the
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_PoisonsDisabled4	General Settings page
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_showPoisonHelp	Show Poisoning Help
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_poisonUseOpts	Poison Use Options
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_confMsg	Confirmation messages
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_allowPoisonSwitch	Allow poison switching
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_allowPoisonTopup	Allow poison top-up
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_poisonChargeOpts	Poison Charge Options
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_chargePerVial	Charges per vial
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_chrgs	charges
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_chargeMult	Charge Multiplier
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_baseChrgs	base charges
$iEquip_MCM_rep_lbl_poisonIndStyle	Poison indicator style
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_useLargSoul	Select whether to use the largest soul that will fit into the weapon, or to use up your smaller souls first.
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_useOvrsizSoul	Disabling this will stop you from wasting souls which are larger than the charge required to completely refill the weapon
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_usePartGem	To support GIST - Genuinely Intelligent Soul Trap by opusGlass you can stop iEquip from using partially filled gems allowing GIST to continue filling them
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_showEnchCharge	Choose how you would like the enchantment charge for equipped weapons to be displayed in the widget\nCharge Meters - show custom enchantment charge level meters in the widget\nDynamic Soulgems - show dynamic soulgem icons in the widget which change fill level to indicate the current level of enchantment charge\nVanilla HUD enchantment charge meters will be hidden
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_enableChargeFadeout	With this setting enabled the charge meters will show on equipping an enchanted weapon, but will fade out after the delay set below\nAdditionally you can choose whether to re-show on entering combat or when the current charge is below the low charge threshold if set below.\nDefault: Disabled
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_chargeFadeDelay	Set the delay in seconds before the enchantment bars fade out
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_normFillCol	Set the regular fill colour for the enchantment charge meters in the widget
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_enableCustomFlashCol	When your weapon enchantment charge runs out the meter or soulgem will flash a warning. By default this will match whatever you have set as your fill colour. Enabling this setting allows you to instead set a custom flash color\nDefault: Disabled
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_meterFlashCol	Set a custom colour for the warning flash that displays when the charge on the equipped weapon runs out
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_enableGradientFill	Enables a gradient colour fill in the enchantment bars from regular fill (full) to secondary fill (empty)
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_gradFillCol	Set the secondary fill colour (only used when gradient fill is enabled)
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_changeColLowCharge	Allows the enchantment charge bars to change colour when the charge falls below the level specified below
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_setLowChargeTresh	Set the level below which you would like the enchantment bars to change colour
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_lowFillCol	Set the low charge fill colour for the enchantment charge meters in the widget
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_leftFillDir	Choose the fill direction for the left enchantment charge meter\nRight Fill means the full is right, empty is left.  And vice versa for Left Fill\nCentre Fill means the meter will fill from the centre outwards in both directions\nDefault: Left Fill
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_rightFillDir	Choose the fill direction for the right enchantment charge meter\nRight Fill means the full is right, empty is left.  And vice versa for Left Fill\nCentre Fill means the meter will fill from the centre outwards in both directions\nDefault: Right Fill
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_confMsg	Choose which poisoning confirmation messages to show.\nTop-up & Switch will only show messages when you apply poison to an already poisoned item.\nWith messages turned off iEquip will automatically top up or clean off existing poisons\nDefault: Show All
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_allowPoisonSwitch	With this enabled, if the weapon you are dosing is already poisoned with a different poison you will be given the option to remove the current poison before applying the new one. Otherwise you will need to use up the existing poison before applying a new one\nDefault - On
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_allowPoisonTopup	With this enabled, if the weapon you are dosing is already poisoned with the same poison you will be given the option to top up the current poison. If you choose to do so the doses will stack. As with the Charges Per Vial and Multiplier settings it is entirely up to you how you wish to balance or break your game.\nDefault - Off
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_chargePerVial	Allows you to set the number of charges per vial/application. Use with discretion!\nDefault: Single charge per application (vanilla)
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_chargeMult	Allows you to adjust iEquip poison dosing to match any perk overhauls you may be using which affect the Concentrated Poison perk or add new perks which multiply the number of charges per application. If left set at 1 iEquip will check whether the player has the Concentrated Poison perk and apply the vanilla x2 multiplier if you do.\nDefault: 1x (vanilla)
$iEquip_MCM_rep_txt_poisonIndStyle	Choose how the poison charges will be displayed in the left and right slots if you have a poisoned weapon equipped.\nThe two count options will use the regular counter in either slot but with the count displayed in green.\nThe Multiple Drops option will display one, two or three drops to match the number of remaining charges, and will display three drops and a green plus sign if more than three charges remain.\nDefault: Single Drop & Count

$iEquip_MCM_tch_opt_TorchNothing	Torch/Nothing
$iEquip_MCM_tch_opt_TorchCycle	Torch/Cycle
$iEquip_MCM_tch_opt_CycleLeft	Cycle left hand
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_torchLifeOptions	Torch Life Options
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_torchKeyOptions	Torch Hotkey Options
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_torchDropOptions	Drop Lit Torch Options
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_showTorchMeter	Show torch life meter
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_torchMeterCol	Torch meter fill colour
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_torchMeterFillDir	Torch meter fill direction
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_torchDuration	Torches burn for
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_finiteTorchLife	Finite torch life
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_torchesFade	Fade torch light
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_reequipTorch	Auto re-equip torch
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_realisticEquip	Realistic re-equip
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_realisticEquipDelay	Re-equip delay
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_toggleTorch	Toggle Torch
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_dropLitTorches	Drop lit torches
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_dropLitTorchBehavior	When dropping torch
$iEquip_MCM_tch_lbl_realisticTorches	Realistic Torches
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_showTorchMeter	When you equip a torch a meter will show in the left slot displaying the remaining torch life
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_torchMeterCol	Set the fill colour for the torch meter
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_torchMeterFillDir	Set the fill direction for the torch meter
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_setTorchDuration	The vanilla torch has a duration of four minutes, however quite often other mods adjust this to values which make the torches almost ever-lasting.  This allows you to reduce how long each torch will burn for.
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_finiteTorchLife	This removes the vanilla never-ending torch exploit whereby you could simply unequip and re-equip the same torch to reset the torch timer.  With this enabled torches will always run out when the timer expires, no matter how many times you unequip and re-equip them.  When the timer runs out one torch is removed from your inventory, and the timer resets ready for the next one.
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_torchesFade	As the torch timer runs out the light given off by your torch will begin to fade
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_reequipTorch	When your current torch runs out, if you have another one in your inventory, your next torch will be equipped automatically
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_realisticEquip	When equipping the next torch there will be a short, immersive delay as you fumble for it in the dark
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_dropLitTorches	With a torch equipped double tap your left hotkey to drop the current lit torch.  If you enable the torch toggle hotkey then you can also double tap it to drop a torch.
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_dropLitTorchBehavior	Choose what happens with your left hand after dropping the torch.  Do Nothing - Left hand remains empty.  Torch/Nothing - Equip another torch if you have one, otherwise Do Nothing.  Torch/Cycle - Equip another torch if you have one, otherwise cycle left slot forwards. Cycle - Cycle to the next item in the left queue.  QuickShield - Equip a shield or ward, based on your QuickShield preferences.
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_toggleTorchHotKey	Assigning a hotkey here allows you to then single tap to equip a torch, and tap again to switch back to your previously equipped item.  Double tapping this key whilst you have a torch equipped allows you to drop a lit torch.
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_realisticTorches	Realistic Torches has been detected in your load order.  Now if you pick up a burnt out torch from iEquip it will be replaced in your inventory with one of Realistic Torches re-craftable Burnt Out Torch misc items.
$iEquip_MCM_tch_txt_noRealisticTorches	For an even more immersive torch experience we highly recommend installing Realistic Torches by simsim899.  This mod adds the possibility of your torch being extinguished in the rain, blown out by wind or shouting, sound effects, re-craftable burnt out torches and more.

$iEquip_MCM_lbl_Info	Information
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_version	iEquip version
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_presets	MCM Profiles
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_savepreset	Save current MCM settings
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_loadpreset	Load MCM settings from preset
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_deletepreset	Delete MCM settings preset
$iEquip_MCM_inf_txt_savepreset	Save your current MCM settings.  Profiles are saved as .IEQS files in Data/iEquip/MCM Settings allowing you to easily set things up on a new game, or transfer settings between saves.
$iEquip_MCM_inf_txt_loadpreset	Load an MCM Profile.
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_noLoad	Exit without loading a preset
$iEquip_MCM_inf_txt_deletepreset	Delete the selected profile.
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_noDelete	Exit without deleting anything
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_maintenance	Maintenance
$iEquip_MCM_inf_lbl_rstLayout	Reset default iEquip layout
$iEquip_MCM_inf_txt_rstLayout	Selecting this will nuke any changes you have made to iEquip and fully restore the default layout
$iEquip_MCM_inf_msg_rstLayout	Are you sure you wish to completely reset iEquip and discard any layout changes you have made?

$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_restore	Restore
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_fortify	Fortify
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_regen	Regenerate
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_fadeicon	Fade icon
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_hideIcon	Hide icon
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_leaveIcon	Don't fade or hide
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_alwaysStrongest	Strongest
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_smartSelect	Smart Select
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_alwaysWeakest	Weakest
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_alwaysShowSelector	Always show
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_consOrShowSelector	Consume or show
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_consAndShowSelector	Always consume & show
$iEquip_MCM_pot_opt_smartConsAndShowSelector	Smart consume & show
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_potOpts	Potion Group Options
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_enblPotionGroup	Enable Potion Grouping
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_checkAllEffects	Include multi-effect potions
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_exclRestAllEffects	Exclude 'Restore All' potions
$iEquip_pot_msg_addRestAllToGroups	If you have Restore All potions in your inventory and wish them to be added into the potion groups simply drop one of each and pick them back up and they will be added to the groups automatically
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_PotionSelect	Which potion to consume
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_potSelOpts	Potion Type Selector Options
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_showSelector	When to show
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_SmartConsumeThreshold	Smart Consume threshold
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_selectorFadeDelay	Potion type selector fadeout
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_thrshldFX	Stat Level & Active Effect Checks
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_StatThreshold	Stat threshold
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_blockIfRestEffect	Don't consume if restore effect active
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_addCombatException	Skip restore effect check if in combat
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_blockIfBuffEffect	Don't consume if buff effect active
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_addHealthGroup	Add back Health Potions group
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_addStaminaGroup	Add back Stamina Potions group
$iEquip_MCM_gen_lbl_addMagickaGroup	Add back Magicka Potions group
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_whenNoPotions	When no potions left...
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_consIcoFade	Consumable icon fade
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_warningOnLastPotion	Warning flash when last potion used
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_enblRestPotWarn	Low Restore potions warning system
$iEquip_MCM_pot_lbl_lowRestPotNot	Show warning notifications
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_checkAllEffects	For potions with multiple effects where the primary effect is not a health/magicka/stamina restore/fortify/regen effect all effects will be checked. If one or more of the other effects are found to be a health/magicka/stamina restore/fortify/regen effect the potion will be included in the Potion Groups for that effect.  If more than one matching additional effect is found priority will be given to restore effects.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_exclRestAllEffects	Enable if you do not want the strongest Restore All potions to be included in your Potion Groups.  You can still add them manually to your consumables queue through the inventory menu, or if you have Auto-Add Potions enabled in the Queue Options page.  If you currently have them included in your Potion Groups and you turn this off they will be removed from the groups and added to the consumable queue if Auto-Add Potions is enabled
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_showSelector	Always show - the potion type selector is displayed, nothing is consumed\nConsume or Show - Consume a restore potion if required, otherwise show the selector\nAlways Consume & Show - the selector is displayed, and a restore potion is consumed if required\nSmart Consume & Show - the selector is displayed, and a restore potion is consumed if stat is below the consume threshold\nPotion selection always follows your Strongest/Weakest/SmartSelect setting
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_SmartConsumeThreshold	If Smart Consume & Show is selected above, and the stat matching the currently displayed Potion Group is below this level, holding the consumable key will show the potion type selector and at the same time select and consume the most appropriate restore potion. If the stat is above this level then the selector will show and nothing will be consumed.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_selectorFadeDelay	Set the delay in seconds if nothing is consumed before the potion type selector fades out and you return to cycling the consumables queue as normal.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_PotionSelect	Which potion to consume when you hold the Consumable hotkey with one of the Potion Groups showing.\n'Smart Select' allows you to set a stat percentage threshold above which, if you are not in combat, the weakest potion will be consumed.  If your current stat level is below the threshold, or if you are in combat, then the strongest potion needed to restore the stat will be consumed.\n\nDefault: Smart Select
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_StatThreshold	Set the stat (health/magicka/stamina) percentage threshold for Smart Select
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_blockIfRestEffect	When enabled iEquip will check for active effects on the player before consuming a health/magicka/stamina restore potion, and will not consume a potion if the same effect is already active. This stops potions being wasted when playing with overhauls or mods which do not allow same effects to stack, or which use restore over time effects.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_addCombatException	Adds an exception to the active restore effect checks when you are in combat and below the SmartSelect threshold to allow you to consume a potion with a stronger effect than the one currently active on the player.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_blockIfBuffEffect	When enabled iEquip will check for active effects on the player before consuming a health/magicka/stamina fortify or regen potion, and will not consume a potion if the same effect is already active. This stops potions being wasted when playing with overhauls or mods which do not allow same effects to stack.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_addHealthGroup	You have previously removed the Health Potions group from your consumables queue. Use this to add it back in.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_addStaminaGroup	You have previously removed the Stamina Potions group from your consumables queue. Use this to add it back in.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_addMagickaGroup	You have previously removed the Magicka Potions group from your consumables queue. Use this to add it back in.
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_consIcoFade	Choose how much you would like the consumable icon faded out by if displaying an empty potion group.\nDefault: 70%
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_alwaysUse	Choose to always consume the strongest or weakest potion of whichever effect is found based on your order of preference and whatever you have in your inventory at the time
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_whenNoPotions	When you run out of health, stamina or magicka potions you can choose to either fade out the icon for the relevant potion group, or hide it in which case it will not appear while cycling until you have more potions back in your inventory
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_warningOnLastPotion	The potion icon will flash twice when the final health, stamina or magicka potion in your inventory is used before fading or hiding
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_enblRestPotWarn	When potion groups are enabled you will be warned when you are running low on Restore potions for any group. At 5 potions remaining the group count will turn yellow, at 2 it will turn orange, and at 0 it will turn red (it will still show the correct full group count). Additionally if you have flash warning enabled the warning flash will play at each threshold.  Both of these only apply if the relevant potion group is currently displayed in the consumable slot
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_lowRestPotNot	In addition to the count colour and warning flash notifications will be displayed warning you at each threshold that you are running low, almost out or all out of restore potions.  These will display regardless of what is currently showing in the consumable slot.

$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_queLenOpts	Queue Length Options
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_maxItmQue	Max items per queue
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_max	Max
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_items	items
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_hrdLimQueSize	Hard limit queue size
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_addToQueOpts	Add To Queue Options
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_showConfMsg	Show confirmation messages
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_signlBothQue	Single items in both hand queues
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_allow1hSwitch	Allow 1h items to switch hands
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_cacheBlkLst	Item Caching & Blacklisting
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_allowCacheRmvItm	Allow caching of removed items
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_MaxItmCache	Max items to cache
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_enblBlacklist	Blacklist manually removed items
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_clearBlacklist	Reset blacklist
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_autoAddOpts	Auto Add Options
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_autoAddHandItems	Auto-add hand items on equipping
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_autoAddShouts	Auto-add shouts on equipping
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_autoAddPowers	Auto-add powers on equipping
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_autoAddPotions	Auto-add potions
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_autoAddPoisons	Auto-add poisons
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_autoAddConsumables	Auto-add food and drink
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_queueMenuAAFlags	Mark Auto-Added items in queue menus
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_skipAutoAddedItems	Skip auto-added items when cycling
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_maxItmQue	Select the maximum number of items you can add to each slot queue.  Bear in mind adding too many items will mean having to cycle through a LOT to get to what you want. You can set a higher limit and not fill the queue as empty slots will be ignored when cycling.\nDefault = 12
$iEquip_MCM_que_msg_maxItmQue	You are about to reduce the maximum permitted queue length!\n\nAny queues which currently exceed the new length will be trimmed.\n\nDo you wish to proceed?
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_hrdLimQueSize	Hard limit the queue lengths to the value set above. Disabling this will allow your queues to grow dynamically if you enable auto adding of new items below\nDefault: On
$iEquip_MCM_que_msg_hrdLimQueSize	You are about to enable a hard limit on your maximum queue lengths!\n\nDoing so will stop the queues from being able to grow organically as new items are equipped. This can particularly affect your consumable and poison queues.\n\nDo you wish to proceed?
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_showConfMsg	Disabling this removes the confirmation messageboxes when adding items to the queues, removing items or clearing the queues
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_signlBothQue	Allow adding the same 1h item to both the left and right hand queues if you only have one of them in your inventory\nDefault: Off
$iEquip_MCM_que_msg_signlBothQue	iEquip Queue Maintenance\n\nWould you like us to check now and remove duplicate items which you only have one of? Priority will be given to the left hand queue as we are only looking at 1h items here, so they will be removed from your right queue.
$iEquip_MCM_que_btn_purge	Purge Queues
$iEquip_MCM_que_btn_leave	Leave In Both
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_allow1hSwitch	If you have allowed single items in both queues this setting determines whether you want those items to be able to switch hands, or if you want cycling to skip past them if they are already equipped in the other hand.\nDefault: Off
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_autoAddHandItems	Enabling this setting will allow any manually equipped item which isn't already found in your left/right queue to be automatically added to the queue. Hand items will only be added if not found in either queue. Items added this way will allow the queue length to grow if you have disabled the hard limit above.\nDefault: On
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_autoAddShouts	Enabling this setting will allow any manually equipped shout which isn't already found in your shout/power queue to be automatically added to the queue.\nDefault: On
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_autoAddPowers	Enabling this setting will allow any manually equipped power which isn't already found in your shout/power queue to be automatically added to the queue.\nDefault: On
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_autoAddPotions	With this enabled all potions not covered by the Health, Magicka and Stamina Potion Groups will be automatically added to your consumables queue.  In addition, if Potion Grouping is disabled, or if the individual group matching the added potion type is disabled, then these potions will also be added directly to the consumable queue. Re-enabling Potion Groups will then give you the option to remove the individual potions from the consumable queue
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_autoAddPoisons	With this enabled iEquip will manage your poison queue for you, finding and adding all poisons currently in your inventory and adding new ones as you acquire them. There will no longer be a restriction on the number of poisons in the queue, and they will be sorted alphabetically.  If you intend to grind alchemy then disable this setting, however if you only craft and carry poisons you intend to use then this will save you having to manage the poison queue.\nDefault - On
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_autoAddConsumables	With this enabled iEquip will add food and drink to your consumables queue for you, finding and adding all food and drink currently in your inventory and adding new ones as you acquire them. There will no longer be a restriction on the number of items in the queue.  If you regularly carry lots of different food and drink items then disable this setting, however if you only carry what you intend to eat and drink then this will save you having to manage those items in the consumables queue.\nDefault - On
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_queueMenuAAFlags	The queue menus will show (A) ahead of the item names for any items which have been Auto-Added to the queue.  This is really only of any interest if you currently have 'Skip Auto-Added Items enabled below'.\nNote - you can remove the auto-added flag from an item at any time by opening your Inventory Menu, highlighting the item and pressing the relevant queue hotkey.
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_skipAutoAddedItems	Enabling this will cause auto added items in your left, right and shout queues to be ignored when cycling.  This is useful if you use a hotkey equipping mod alongside iEquip to do the actual equipping, and use the iEquip widget more as a visual aid.  Directly equipped items will show in the widget as normal, and you can then use the cycle keys to cycle a smaller set of items manually added to the queues if so desired.
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_allowCacheRmvItm	Each time you cycle IEquip checks if you still have the item and if not removes it from your queues. This allows caching of those removed items so if you later add them back into your inventory they will automatically be added back into the queue they were previously in as long as there is space in the queue or you have disabled the hard limit.\nDefault: On
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_MaxItmCache	Determines the maximum number of removed items you want to remember\nDefault: 60 items
$iEquip_MCM_que_txt_enblBlacklist	Items which you manually remove from your queues using the Remove From Queue option in the queue menus will be added to a blacklist so they are not Auto-Added if you subsequently manually re-equip or re-acquire them.  You can remove individual items from the blacklist simply by manually re-adding them using the hotkey method in the Inventory or Magic menus
$iEquip_MCM_pot_txt_clearBlacklist	You currently have items in your blacklist.  This will clear all items from the blacklist. If you would rather just remove individual items from the blacklist you can do so by simply manually re-adding them using the hotkey method in the Inventory or Magic menus
$iEquip_MCM_que_lbl_cachedItms	cached items

$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_preselect	Preselect
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_equip	Equip
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_left	in your left hand
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_right	in your right hand
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_both	in both hands
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_whereFound	where it is found
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_bow	Bow
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_crossbow	Crossbow
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_boundBow	Bound Bow
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_boundCrossbow	Bound Crossbow
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_switch	Switch Back
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_2h	Two Handed
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_1h	One Handed
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_spell	Spell
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_eitherBuff	Fortify or Regen
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_fortifyOnly	Fortify only
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_regenOnly	Regen only
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_bothBuffs	Fortify & Regen
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_alwaysQB	Always QuickBuff
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_QBOn2ndPress	On 2nd Press
$iEquip_MCM_pro_opt_2ndPressInCombat	2nd Press In Combat
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_dragEastrA	Here be dragons...
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_dragEastrB	Wait, what are you doing...
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_dragEastrC	You're not seriously going in there?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_dragEastrD	Have you lost your mind?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_dragEastrE	I really don't think you should...
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_dragEastrF	Do you EVER listen?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_dragEastrG	Fine, have it your way...
$iEquip_MCM_pro_msg_dragEastr	iEquip Advanced Features unlocked!\n\nYour dogged determination has paid off, friend. You now have access to everything iEquip has to offer.\n\nLet the games begin!
$iEquip_MCM_pro_msg_dragEastr_SE	Please exit out of the Journal Menu, then re-open the iEquip MCM to finish enabling the Advanced Features
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblProMode	Enable Advanced Features
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblProMode	Enabling Advanced Mode unlocks many additional features and options including Preselect Mode, QuickShield, QuickRanged, QuickRestore/QuickBuff and QuickDualCast\nDefault = Off
$iEquip_MCM_pro_msg_enblProMode	iEquip Advanced Features disabled!\n\nPlease exit and reopen the MCM.
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_whatIsProMode	What are the Advanced Features?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_preselectOpts	Preselect Options
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_whatPreselect	What is Preselect?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblPreselect	Enable Preselect
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblShoutPreselect	Enable shout preselect
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_swapPreselectItm	Swap preselect with current item
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_eqpAllExitPreselectMode	Equip All Exits Preselect Mode
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickShieldOpts	QuickShield Options
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_whatQuickshield	What is QuickShield?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblQuickshield	Enable QuickShield
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_with2hReqp	With 2H/ranged equipped
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_ifNotFound	Unequip left hand if nothing found
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_prefMag	Prefer magic
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_rightHandspllTyp	Right hand spell type
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_inPreselect	In Preselect Mode
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickRestoreOpts	QuickRestore Options
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_whatQuickRestore	What is QuickRestore?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblQuickRestore	Enable QuickRestore
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblQuickheal	- Include QuickHeal
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblQuickMagicka	- Include QuickMagicka
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblQuickStamina	- Include QuickStamina
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_QuickRestoreThreshold	Stat threshold for QuickRestore
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickBuff	Enable QuickBuff
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickBuffControl	QuickBuff Activation
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickBuffDelay	2nd press within
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_buffsToApply	Which buffs to apply
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickHealOpts	QuickHeal Options
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_useFallback	Use either healing method
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_alwysEqpSpll	Always equip spell...
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_swtchBck	Switch Back
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_swtchBckRest	Restore when switching back
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickRangedOpts	QuickRanged Options
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_whatQuickranged	What is QuickRanged?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblQuickranged	Enable QuickRanged
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_prefWepTyp	Preferred weapon type
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_swtchOut	Switch out options
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_prefMagSchl	Preferred magic school
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_quickDCOpts	QuickDualCast Options
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_whatQuickdualcast	What is QuickDualCast?
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enblQuickdualcast	Enable QuickDualCast
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_enableQDCSchools	Enable QuickDualCast for:
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_altSpll	   Alteration spells
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_conjSpll	   Conjuration spells
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_destSpll	   Destruction spells
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_illSpll	   Illusion spells
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_restSpll	   Restoration spells
$iEquip_MCM_pro_lbl_reqBothQue	Only if in both queues
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_whatProMode	What are the Advanced Features?\n\nThey are a suite of advanced, quick access functions and settings which allow you to fully unleash the power of iEquip.
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblPreselect	Enable/disable Preselect and the associated options. For a full description of what Preselect is and what it does read the Help notes\nDefault = Off
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblShoutPreselect	If you only want Preselect to be available on your left/right hand slots you can choose to disable preselect altogether on the shout slot\nDefault = On
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_swapPreselectItm	The normal behaviour when equipping a preselected item is to then advance the preselect slot on to the next item in the queue. With this enabled it will instead swap the currently equipped item to the preselect slot, allowing you to swap back and forth between the two items. You can still cycle the preselect slot as normal.\nDefault: Off
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_eqpAllExitPreselectMode	Enabling this will toggle you back out of Preselect Mode whenever you use Equip All Preselected Items. It still allows you to equip individual preselected items as many times as you like, and you can still toggle out of Preselect Mode manually at any time by pressing and holding your Consumables hotkey.\nDefault: Disabled
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblQuickshield	Enable/disable QuickShield and the associated options. For a full description of what QuickShield is and what it does read the Help notes\nDefault = Off
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_prefShieldMag	With this enabled QuickShield will always look for a ward spell first and will also check what's in your right hand and look for a suitable spell to equip as well if needed.\nDefault = Off
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_with2hReqp	With this enabled if QuickShield is used while wielding a 2H or ranged weapon iEquip will look for a suitable 1H item or spell and equip that in your right hand at the same time\nDefault = On
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_rightHandspllTyp	If you have enabled Prefer Magic then you can also optionally choose a preferred school of magic for your right hand spell. iEquip will look for a spell from that school first and if none found will look for a Destruction spell instead\nDefault = Destruction
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_ifNotFound	With this enabled if QuickShield doesn't find a suitable shield or ward to equip, and you currently have a 1H weapon in your right hand, your left hand will be unequipped allowing you to block with your right hand weapon
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_inPreselectQuickshieldMode	Choose the preffered behaviour of QuickShield when used in Preselect Mode\nDefault = Preselect
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblQuickRestore	QuickRestore is an advanced situationally aware feature giving you the ability to quickly restore or buff all three stats at once based on several variables
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblQuickheal	QuickRestore will look for the best way to restore or buff your Health
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblQuickMagicka	QuickRestore will look for the best way to restore or buff your Magicka
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblQuickStamina	QuickRestore will look for the best way to restore or buff your Stamina
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_QuickRestoreThreshold	When your weapons are drawn QuickRestore will only look to restore stats which are currently below this level
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_quickBuff	When enabled, if your weapons are not drawn QuickRestore will look for Fortify or Regen Rate potions to buff each stat allowing you to quickly prepare ahead of combat
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_quickBuffControl	Always QuickBuff - QuickRestore will restore all enabled stats as required and then proceed to buff each in turn\nQuickBuff on 2nd press - The first time you activate QuickRestore it will restore all enabled stats as required. Activating a second time within the specified 2nd Press period will then proceed to buff each stat in turn\n2nd Press In Combat - Always QuickBuff applies when not in combat, QuickBuff on 2nd press applies when in combat
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_quickBuffDelay	Set the length of time in seconds following a QuickRestore activation during which if you triple press your consumable key again QuickBuff will be activated
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_buffsToApply	Choose which buffs you want QuickBuff to apply.  Either will look for a fortify potion first and if it doesn't find one will then look for a regen one, but will only consume one or other not both.
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_prefHealMag	With this enabled iEquip will look for a healing spell in either hand queue and equip it according to your preferences set below. If it doesn't find a suitable spell it will then look for a health potion to consume as a last resort
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_useFallback	Allow QuickHeal to look for an alternative healing method if your first choice method cannot be found (ie potions instead of healing spells, and vice versa)
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_alwysEqpSpll	Decide whether you would like the healing spell to be equipped in the hand it is found in, in a specific hand every time or dual casting
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_swtchBck	Enabling this will allow you to switch back to your previously equipped items by triple pressing the consumable key for a second time after you have finished healing. Only applies if a healing spell has been equipped.  If a potion has been consumed this will do nothing.
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_swtchBckRest	As well as switching back to your previous items QuickRestore will also find and consume a Restore Magicka potion to give you a quick boost to Magicka after using your healing spell
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblQuickranged	Enabling this will allow you to switch back to your previously equipped items by triple pressing the consumable key for a second time after you have finished healing. Only applies if a healing spell has been equipped.  If a potion has been consumed this will do nothing.
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_enblQuickdualcast	Enable/disable QuickDualCast and the associated options. For a full description of what QuickDualCast is and what it does read the Help notes\nDefault = Off
$iEquip_MCM_pro_txt_reqBothQue	By default QuickDualCast will dual equip spells from your chosen schools in both hands regardless of whether the spell is on one or both queues. Enabling this restricts QuickDualCast to only spells which are found in both left and right hand queues.\nDefault = Off